const questionData = [
    {
    question: "In a typical neuron, the __ receive(s) information and the __ communicate(s) that information to a neighboring cell.",
    options: [
        "axon; cell body",
        "axon; dendrites",
        "dendrites; axon",
        "dendrites; cell body",
        "cell body; dendrites"
    ],
    answer: "dendrites; axon",
    image: ""
},
{
    question: "In several neurological diseases, axons lose their insulating myelin sheath. What is the consequence of this loss?",
    options: [
        "Nerve cells lose too much heat.",
        "Nerve cells retain too much heat.",
        "Action potential transmission slows down.",
        "Action potential transmission speeds up"
    ],
    answer: "Action potential transmission slows down."
},
{
    question: "A neurotransmitter travels from a sending cell to a receiving cell, causing Na+ ions to pour into the receiving cell. As a result, an action potential in the receiving cell becomes ______ likely.",
    options: [
        "more",
        "less",
        "equally"
    ],
    answer: "more"
},
{
    question: "Underdevelopment of the medulla oblongata could lead to",
    options: [
        "poor processing of sensory information.",
        "limited language skills.",
        "erratic changes in blood pressure.",
        "unconscious muscle movements"
    ],
    answer: "erratic changes in blood pressure."
},
{
    question: "Which of the following items are NOT part of the central nervous system?",
    options: [
        "Sensory neurons",
        "Cerebrum",
        "Brainstem",
        "Hypothalamus",
        "All of these are part of the central nervous system"
    ],
    answer: "Sensory neurons"
},
{
    question: "Suppose a hormone released by the pancreas can alter metabolism in the liver. Which of the following statements is incorrect?",
    options: [
        "The target cells are in the pancreas.",
        "Certain liver cells have receptor proteins that recognize only that hormone.",
        "The hormone could be detected in blood taken from a person’s arm.",
        "The hormone changes liver cell metabolism."
    ],
    answer: "The target cells are in the pancreas."
},
{
    question: "Doctors must remove part of a man’s posterior pituitary. What is the most likely long-term consequence of this surgery?",
    options: [
        "The hypothalamus will produce fewer inhibiting hormones.",
        "The hypothalamus will produce fewer releasing hormones.",
        "Too much water will be lost in urine.",
        "The thyroid will be under-stimulated.",
        "Sex hormones will be under-produced."
    ],
    answer: "Too much water will be lost in urine."
},
{
    question: "In type II diabetes, a person’s cells become insensitive to insulin released by the pancreas. What is the consequence?",
    options: [
        "Blood sugar rises because the liver releases more sugar.",
        "Blood sugar rises because cells fail to absorb sugar from the bloodstream.",
        "Blood sugar drops because the liver absorbs more sugar.",
        "Blood sugar drops because cells absorb too much sugar from the bloodstream."
    ],
    answer: "Blood sugar rises because cells fail to absorb sugar from the bloodstream."
},
{
    question: "What is the role of the zygote in the sexual life cycle?",
    options: [
        "It produces the male gametes.",
        "It produces the female gametes.",
        "It is the first cell of a new offspring.",
        "It is the first differentiated cell of a new offspring.",
        "It represents the last stage in reproduction before fertilization."
    ],
    answer: "It is the first cell of a new offspring."
},
{
    question: "A sperm cell passes through multiple tubes along its journey in the male reproductive system. Which of the following comes last in the sequence?",
    options: [
        "Testes",
        "Urethra",
        "Epididymis",
        "Vas deferens",
        "Seminiferous tubule"
    ],
    answer: "Urethra"
},
{
    question: "If the egg is not fertilized, then lowered progesterone and estrogen levels enable GnRH to be released from the Blank, and then FSH and LH released from the Blank.",
    options: [
        "hypothalamus; anterior pituitary",
        "anterior pituitary; ovaries",
        "ovaries; uterine lining",
        "hypothalamus; ovaries",
        "ovaries; anterior pituitary"
    ],
    answer: "hypothalamus; anterior pituitary"
},
{
    question: "Fertilization occurs in the",
    options: [
        "seminiferous tubule.",
        "endometrium.",
        "uterine tube.",
        "ovary.",
        "vagina."
    ],
    answer: "uterine tube."
},
{
    question: "Which does NOT participate in immunity?",
    options: [
        "Lymphocytes",
        "Lymphoid organs",
        "Macrophages",
        "Red blood cells"
    ],
    answer: "Red blood cells"
},
{
    question: "Antihistamines are drugs that block the action of histamines. Taking an antihistamine should therefore prevent",
    options: [
        "fluid from leaking from your bloodstream into your body’s tissues.",
        "fever.",
        "pathogens from outcompeting your resident microbes.",
        "cancer"
    ],
    answer: "fluid from leaking from your bloodstream into your body’s tissues."
},
{
    question: "Which of the following participates in both innate immunity and adaptive immunity?",
    options: [
        "Antibodies",
        "Macrophages",
        "Helper T cells",
        "Memory B cells",
        "Cytotoxic T cells"
    ],
    answer: "Helper T cells"
},
{
    question: "Influenza (flu) is caused by the influenza virus. A flu vaccine contains Blank from inactivated Blank.",
    options: [
        "antibodies; viruses",
        "antigens; antibodies",
        "viruses; antigens",
        "antibodies; B cells",
        "antigens; viruses"
    ],
    answer: "viruses; antigens"
},
{
    question: "A person who is born without B cells or T cells has",
    options: [
        "an immunodeficiency.",
        "an autoimmune disorder.",
        "an allergy.",
        "HIV/AIDS."
    ],
    answer: "an immunodeficiency."
},
{
    question: "What component of blood is matched correctly with one of its functions?",
    options: [
        "Red blood cell: initiates clotting",
        "White blood cell: produces antibodies",
        "Platelet: carries oxygen and carbon dioxide",
        "Plasma: engulfs and destroys foreign substances"
    ],
    answer: "White blood cell: produces antibodies"
},
{
    question: "Which of the following statements about the human circulatory system is true?",
    options: [
        "Diffusion occurs rapidly across artery walls into body cells.",
        "Veins always carry blood away from the heart.",
        "Our circulatory system is open because the lungs are open to the atmosphere.",
        "The heart pumps blood directly into arteries."
    ],
    answer: "The heart pumps blood directly into arteries."
},
  {
    question: "A red blood cell is in the heart’s right ventricle. When it next enters the heart, which heart chamber will it enter?",
    options: [
      "Left atrium",
      "Right atrium",
      "Left ventricle",
      "Right ventricle"
    ],
    answer: "Left atrium"
  },
  {
    question: "Breathing rate is mostly determined by:",
    options: [
      "the concentration of O2 in the air.",
      "the concentration of CO2 in the blood.",
      "the concentration of O2 in the blood.",
      "the amount of hemoglobin in the blood."
    ],
    answer: "the concentration of CO2 in the blood."
  },
  {
    question: "Roots depend on shoots because shoots _____, which is transported to the roots.",
    options: [
      "absorb water from the soil",
      "produce hormones for root growth",
      "produce sugar",
      "store excess nutrients"
    ],
    answer: "produce sugar"
  },
  {
    question: "Plants require abundant carbon and nitrogen. These elements occur in some of the same molecules, including:",
    options: [
      "Water, glucose, and oxygen.",
      "Proteins, ATP, and DNA.",
      "Cellulose, starch, and lipids.",
      "Vitamins, minerals, and enzymes."
    ],
    answer: "Proteins, ATP, and DNA."
  },
  {
    question: "If you cut a stalk of celery and put it in a glass of water containing red food coloring overnight, the next morning the celery will be red. The food coloring is taken up through the...",
    options: [
      "phloem.",
      "cambium.",
      "xylem.",
      "parenchyma."
    ],
    answer: "xylem."
  },
  {
    question: "Why are root tips ideal specimens for looking at the phases of mitosis?",
    options: [
      "They are easily stained for microscopic viewing.",
      "They contain cells that are fully differentiated.",
      "They contain lots of rapidly dividing cells.",
      "They are less prone to contamination."
    ],
    answer: "They contain lots of rapidly dividing cells."
  },
  {
    question: "The transportation of water in xylem from root to leaf using Cohesion force between water molecules.",
    options: [
      "This statement is false because water is transported by adhesion.",
      "This statement is true.",
      "This statement is false because water is transported by root pressure only.",
      "This statement is false because cohesion only applies to phloem transport."
    ],
    answer: "This statement is true."
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following represents the correct order of organization of an animal's body?",
    options: [
      "Organs; tissues; cells; organ systems",
      "Cells; organs; tissues; organ systems",
      "Cells; tissues; organs; organ systems",
      "Tissues; cells; organs; organ systems"
    ],
    answer: "Cells; tissues; organs; organ systems"
  },
  {
    question: "Bone is best described as __________ tissue.",
    options: [
      "epithelial",
      "muscular",
      "nervous",
      "connective"
    ],
    answer: "connective"
  },
  {
    question: "If your kidneys failed to function what would you expect to happen in your body?",
    options: [
      "You would not be able to regulate your body temperature.",
      "You would not be able to remove oxygen from your blood.",
      "You would not be able to remove nitrogenous waste from your blood.",
      "You would not be able to produce digestive enzymes."
    ],
    answer: "You would not be able to remove nitrogenous waste from your blood."
  },
  {
    question: "If blood pH is controlled by negative feedback, then when your blood becomes too acidic:",
    options: [
      "you should crave sour beverages.",
      "your kidney should remove H+ ions from the blood.",
      "your rate of digestion should slow.",
      "your heart rate should increase."
    ],
    answer: "your kidney should remove H+ ions from the blood."
  },
  {
    question: "What system does not involve in the respiratory system to exchange gases?",
    options: [
      "Circulatory system",
      "Nervous system",
      "Urinary system",
      "Muscular system"
    ],
    answer: "Urinary system"
  },
  {
    question: "Why is it important to have a varied diet?",
    options: [
      "To ensure you only consume your favorite foods.",
      "So that our body will get all the necessary micro- and macro- nutrients.",
      "To limit your exposure to different food groups.",
      "To simplify meal preparation."
    ],
    answer: "So that our body will get all the necessary micro- and macro- nutrients."
  },
  {
    question: "Once a week, Timothy goes on a pilates session after work. He burns 500 Calories per session. On days that he takes the pilates session, he treats himself to a protein powder milkshake (550 Calories) instead of fake bubble tea (0 calories). Assuming everything else in his diet is the same, predict how his weight will change.",
    options: [
      "He will slowly lose weight.",
      "He will maintain his current weight.",
      "He will slowly gain weight.",
      "His weight will fluctuate unpredictably."
    ],
    answer: "He will slowly gain weight."
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these organs is not involved in the digestive system?",
    options: [
      "Stomach",
      "Liver",
      "Pancreas",
      "Spleen"
    ],
    answer: "Spleen"
  },
  {
    question: "Nitrogenous waste are mostly derived from what?",
    options: [
      "Carbohydrates",
      "Lipids",
      "Proteins",
      "Nucleic Acids"
    ],
    answer: "Proteins"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following substances are not reabsorbed in the nephrons?",
    options: [
      "Glucose",
      "Amino Acids",
      "Water",
      "Hydrogen ions"
    ],
    answer: "Hydrogen ions"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is absent in the plasma?",
    options: [
      "Water",
      "Proteins",
      "Glucose",
      "Platelet"
    ],
    answer: "Platelet"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about the closed circulatory system in an animal?",
    options: [
      "Blood is found freely in body cavities.",
      "It is found in insects.",
      "Found in human.",
      "Gases are exchanged directly between blood and cells."
    ],
    answer: "Found in human."
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the heart chamber receives venous blood from different parts of the body?",
    options: [
      "Left atrium",
      "Left ventricle",
      "Right atrium",
      "Right ventricle"
    ],
    answer: "Right atrium"
  },
  {
    question: "During inhalation, diaphragm  while the muscles between the ribs .",
    options: [
      "relaxes and moves upward; relax",
      "contracts and pulls downward; relax",
      "contracts and pulls downward; contract",
      "relaxes and moves upward; contract"
    ],
    answer: "contracts and pulls downward; contract"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not included in an innate immune response?",
    options: [
      "Phagocytosis",
      "Inflammation",
      "Fever",
      "Antibody"
    ],
    answer: "Antibody"
  },
  {
    question: "In an allergic reaction, mast cells release _, which triggers allergy symptoms.",
    options: [
      "adrenaline",
      "histamine",
      "insulin",
      "serotonin"
    ],
    answer: "histamine"
  }
]

export default questionData